kgmens.com 2013-11-03

# Men's and Women's Clothing, Childrens', Shoes, & Accessories - Designer Suits, Dress Shirts, Pants and dresses - K&G

K&G Fashion Superstore ("K&G", "us", "our", or "we") is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit the KGstores.com website ("Site") or shop at our stores. This privacy policy will help you understand what information is collected when you visit the Site or our stores and how that information will be used. If we adjust this policy at any time in the future, we will post those changes here. Since this policy applies to you, you should review this policy from time to time, as it may be changed.

**Aggregate Non-Personal Information That We Collect**

"Aggregate non-personal information" is information that is recorded about users and collected into groups so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user. We collect the following information from visitors to our site:

  * Aggregated non-personal information on those pages visitors access.
  * Information volunteered by visitors during registration.

**Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect**

When you register for services (like becoming a member of the K&G Rewards program) or purchase products from K&G, the following information is collected:

  * Name
  * Mailing / Shipping Address
  * Telephone Number
  * E-mail Address
  * Birth Month
  * Credit Card Information
  * Information volunteered by visitors during registration.

For example, when you visit our Site and shop online with K&G, we will ask you to submit certain information identified above in order to properly process your order. If necessary, we will contact you via telephone or e-mail to request any information needed to fulfill and ship your merchandise or to advise you of any delays to the shipment anticipated. Additionally, we may contact you after your order has shipped to ensure that your order was received in good condition and in a timely manner. In all events, we will keep the information you submit on a secured server and your credit card information will be encrypted.

You may view, change, or delete your personal information at any time by contacting us by email, mail or phone. See "For Further Information" below for contact information.

**Other Information We Collect**

We also automatically receive and record from your browser, including your IP address, Internet connection speed, and Internet connection duration.

**Sharing Information**

At K&G, we are committed to protecting our relationship with our customers, and we use personally identifiable information that you submitted as part of our own business or that of a parent or affiliate company. From time to time we share aggregate non-personal and personally identifiable information with our parent and affiliates to assist in our marketing and merchandising efforts. In addition, in the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by K&G or any affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, both personally identifiable information and aggregate non-personal information from and/or about our customers may be among the transferred assets.

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information or aggregate non-personal information when (a) we believe the law requires such disclosure, (b) in response to legal process and law enforcement requests, and (c) as necessary to protect the property, interests, and rights of K&G, its parent and affiliates, and others. We also transfer your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties to (a) assist us in managing and maintaining customer information, (b) assist us in our own marketing efforts or (c) administer services on our behalf, such as credit card processing for purchases. We do not, however, authorize those parties to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. That said, we may rent or sell to third parties aggregate non-personal information about visitors to the Site without restriction as to use.

Except as set forth in this policy, at no time will we disseminate personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for any reason.

Please contact us for any additional questions about the management or use of personally identifiable information, or if you do not wish to have your personally identifiable information shared. See "For Further Information," below for contact information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file that our web server will store on your computer to give you an individual ID and save certain information about previous visits. A cookie will store useful information, including some personal information, which enables our Web site to remember you when you return to visit. K&G Fashion Superstore does not share this information with any third parties.

If you do not wish to have a cookie on your system, you may be able to set your browser to either refuse cookies in the future, or warn you before accepting a cookie. For further information, please refer to the documentation and help provided with your browser software. In addition, browsers may allow you to delete any cookies they have accumulated during your past Internet excursions. Please note that if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some parts of our site may not work properly.

**Information Security and Notification**

We maintain your information on a secured server, and we encrypt your credit card information. But, there is no perfect security that is impenetrable from hackers and thieves. In the very unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in the possession or control of K&G may have been compromised, K&G may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, K&G may notify you using the information you submitted to K&G.

Other Communications You May Receive

We will occasionally make promotional information available to you through e-mail. However, if you do not want to receive e-mail communications, please indicate the same during the registration process, as appropriate, or contact us using the information at the end of this policy.

**Children's Policy**

We are very concerned about the safety of children using the Internet. In keeping with the Children's Online Protection Act of 1998, we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any visitor under the age of 13 without prior, verifiable, parental consent.

If we discover that a visitor under the age of 13 has registered without parental consent, we will remove his or her registration information from our files. We will then maintain a record of the child's name and address in a DO NOT REGISTER file.

**Links to Other Sites and Services**

This site may at times include links to other sites that are not under our control. These sites have their own policies about privacy and security, which you may review before using those sites. K&G Fashion Superstore assumes no responsibility for these linked sites and provides these links solely for the convenience of our customers.

**Social Security Number Protection Policy**

Social Security numbers are classified as Confidential information by K&G Fashion Superstore. We work hard to protect Social Security numbers, whether in paper or electronic form, and we have policies and procedures that prohibit the unlawful disclosure of and that limit access to Social Security numbers. These restrictions apply to all Social Security numbers collected or retained by K&G Fashion Superstore in connection with customer, employee or other relationships.

**For Further Information**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns or wish to be removed from any mailing lists, please contact us in one of the following ways:

E-mail us: [customerservice@kgstores.com](mailto:customerservice@kgstores.com)

Call us:     1-800-343-3700

Our business hours are:

Monday through Friday: 8:00 A.M. to 11:00 P.M.

Saturday: 9:00 A.M. to 8:00 P.M.

Sunday: 10:00 A.M. to 8:00 P.M.

Write us at:

K&G Fashion Superstore  
Customer Relations  
6380 Rogerdale Rd  
Houston, Texas 77072  
Attn: Online Customer Relations
